Busy Bodies is a comedy film directed by Lloyd French.
In this short film, Laurel and Hardy wage battle with inanimate objects, their
co-workers, and the laws of physics during a routine work day at a sawmill.
Stan, played by Stan Laurel.
Ollie, played by Oliver Hardy.
Shoveler (uncredited), played by Dick Gilbert.
Shop Worker (uncredited), played by Charlie Hall.
Shop Worker (uncredited), played by Jack Hill.
Shop Foreman (uncredited), played by Tiny Sandford.
Busy Bodies is a 1933 American short comedy film starring Laurel and Hardy.
The film explores themes of slapstick comedy, black and
white, sawmill, water leak, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.